

Fatma Sliti Frontend Developer

fatmasliti289@gmail.com

95017336

Tunisia

linkedin.com/in/fatma-sliti-86489b226

github.com/FatmaSliti

From childhood, I've been captivated by design, a passion that now drives my career as a Frontend Developer. My journey from doodling interface ideas to crafting user-centric web designs stems from a lifelong fascination with creating visually compelling digital experiences. Combining this passion with my Computer Science background enables me to translate concepts into captivating interfaces.

Ariana

Tunis

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science (Software Engineering)

Faculty of Sciences, Sfax

09/2021 - 06/2023

High school diploma in Technical Sciences **IBN ABI DHIEF**

2020

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

END-OF-STUDIES INTERNSHIP

Tunisie Télécom

02/2023 - 05/2023

Full-Stack Developer

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

- Website Development for RLA Market Digitalization and Inventory Tracking using React JS Library

SUMMER INTERNSHIP

Bee Coders

06/2022 - 07/2022

Statup

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

Web Development using HTML / CSS / JS

SKILLS



EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

IT, GDSC, IEEE Club (10/2021 - 06/2022) Member

THE REFERENDUM OF JULY 25, 2022

VICE PRESIDENT OF THE POLLING STATION

CETIFICATES

Git & GitHub - The Practical Guide (11/2023 - Present)

React - The Complete Guide 2023 (incl. React Router & Redux) (08/2023 - 10/2023)

LANGUES

Arabe

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Français

Full Professional Proficiency

Anglais

Professional Working Proficiency

Allemand

Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

Leadership

Travelling

Doing good deeds